http://www.trojan.ie/privacy-policy

menu
Industry SolutionsBuilders MerchantsRetailConstruction and EngineeringFinancial ServicesLegalHealth ServicesBusiness Management SoftwareNuage Accounting SoftwareIntact iQIntact xLineAccounts Payable AutomationManaged IT Services IT Support ServicesSecurity SolutionsData Protection and RecoveryModern WorkplaceCloud ComputingCollaborative WorkingBusiness Intelligence
Support
Support
Submit a support ticket
Remote support tool
get in touch
Call us on
071 9662552
contact us
submit a support ticket
menu
Industry SolutionsBuilders MerchantsRetailConstruction and EngineeringFinancial ServicesLegalHealth ServicesBusiness Management SoftwareNuage Accounting SoftwareIntact iQIntact xLineAccounts Payable AutomationManaged IT Services IT Support ServicesSecurity SolutionsData Protection and RecoveryModern WorkplaceCloud ComputingCollaborative WorkingBusiness Intelligence Close
Data Privacy Statement Trojan IT Business Solutions
We review this Privacy Statement regularly. Occasionally we may need to make changes or additions to this Statement that may affect how we handle your data.   We will indicate on this page when the Privacy Statement has changed so please refer to this link for the latest version.
This Privacy Statement was last reviewed and updated in January 2018.
1. What information will Trojan IT collect?
During our relationship with you, we may collect personal information, such as your name, address, telephone, email, IP address and other contact details, and any other information relating to you which you may provide.
2. How do we use this information?
Your personal information may be processed, by Trojan IT, for purposes including: (i) administering our relationship with you; (ii) providing any goods, services or information you have requested; (iii) providing you with information about our products and services; and (iv) for auditing usage of the site.
The transmission of data via the internet is not completely secure and, as such, is at your own risk. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, e.g. through encryption, password protection or limiting access to your information, Trojan IT cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted to our Websites.
Trojan IT has policies and technical measures in place to safeguard and protect your personal information against unauthorised access, accidental loss, improper use and disclosure. We will also take all reasonable precautions to ensure that our staff and employees who have access to information about you have received adequate training.
3. Marketing
The processing of personal data for marketing purposes is carried out in line with legislation and the Data Protection Acts 1988 & 2003 ("The Acts") and Statutory Instrument Number 336 of 2011 European Communities (Electronic Communications Networks and Services) (Privacy and Electronic Communications) Regulations 2011 ("SI 336/2011"). Occasionally, we may contact you with information about other Trojan IT products and services which we think may be of interest to you. However, we will only do so when you have given your prior consent to being contacted in this way and/or subject to relevant legal requirements.
Trojan IT occasionally may email marketing information to subscribers on their database in accordance with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679). All recipients of this material can unsubscribe using the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of all marketing emails received.
4. How we use cookies and similar technologies
Cookies help us understand which sections of our Websites are the most popular, as they help show which pages are being visited and how long for.  This helps Trojan IT adapt our Website to provide more relevant and accessible information. For example, cookies allow us to ensure that the information displayed on your next visit to our Websites will match up with your user preferences.
You may configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Please note, however, that disabling cookies might affect your online experience and/or prevent you from taking full advantage of our site. From time to time we may also use other technologies to log and collect data to analyse traffic to our Websites. These technologies will regularly only allow for an anonymous notice of your visit to be generated. In conjunction with cookies, this will enable us to identify what portions of our Websites are of interest to our visitors and to help us provide you with tailored information from our Websites. For more information about cookies on our site please follow this link.
https://trojan.ie/cookie_policy
5. Your rights
You have a right to request a written copy of the personal information Trojan IT holds about you and to have any inaccurate information about you corrected. You also have the right to request we stop using your details for marketing activities and other promotional activities. You may have further rights regarding the processing of your personal data under applicable law. In case you wish to exercise any such rights, please note the contact information below.
6. Lead Forensics Website Tracking
Contained within our website is a tracking code by Lead Forensics.  This code enables Lead Forensics to track activity on our website and provide and provide Trojan IT Business Solutions Limited with information on the IP address of the requesting computer (this data is not anonymised), the date and duration of the user’s visit, and the web pages which the user visits.  The Lead Forensics tools use IP tracking for identifying businesses and is not the same as cookies.  The Lead Forensics tracking code complies with the data protection act because it only provides information that is readily available in the public domain, it does not, and cannot, provide individual, personal or sensitive data regarding who has visited our website.  It provides information on what the company has visited our website by identifying them from their IP address.  This data may be used by us to contact the business about their experience or marketing purposes.  We will not pass this data to third parties for any reason.  More information can be found at www.leadforencis.com.
7. Contact information
The data controller is Trojan IT. Requests for further information about our Privacy Statement can be emailed to dataprotection@trojan.ie or sent to:
Trojan IT,
Elphin St,
Boyle,
Co. Roscommon,
Ireland
Get in touch
Trojan IT
Boyle
Co Roscommon
Ireland
071 9662552
info@trojan.ie
Our Services
Business Management SoftwareManaged IT Services Modern Workplace
Useful Info
About UsWork With UsSupportContact Us
Join Our Newsletter
Get the latest industry updates and helpful tips direct to your inbox!
Connect with Trojan:
Cookies PolicyPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsMarketing Preferences
© Trojan IT
web design by dmac media
Get In Touch
Call us on
071 9662552
contact us
support
We use necessary cookies to make this site work, we also use optional analytics cookies to enhance user experience - but these are disabled by default See our Cookie Policy
Accept All
Reject All
Settings
